Leser, Paul; Papers ger058
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Series 19 - Materials on various subjects, 19; 188 file folders
  - Theresianstadt / Terezin, Undated (Box 97 (19-Series 19 - Materials on various ), Folder 11)
  - Third Annual Baguio Religious Acculturation Conference, Undated (Box 97 (19-Series 19 - Materials on various ), Folder 12)
  - III. International Atlas Conference for Folk Culture of Europe, Helsinki, May 11-14, 1970 (Box 97 (19-Series 19 - Materials on various ), Folder 13)
  - Threshing, Undated (Box 97 (19-Series 19 - Materials on various ), Folder 14)
  - Translation, Undated (Box 97 (19-Series 19 - Materials on various ), Folder 15)
  - U.N.E.S.C.O. Economic Commission for Africa, Undated (Box 97 (19-Series 19 - Materials on various ), Folder 16)
  - University of Hartford, Undated (Box 97 (19-Series 19 - Materials on various ), Folder 17)
  - 34. Internationaler Amerikanisten-Kongress, Vienna, 1960 July 18-1960 July 25 (Box 97 (19-Series 19 - Materials on various ), Folder 18)
  - Visual anthropology, Undated (Box 97 (19-Series 19 - Materials on various ), Folder 19)
  - Wenner-Gren -- American Anthropological Association -- Ph.D. Curricula Conference, 1958 November 23-1958 November 24 (Box 97 (19-Series 19 - Materials on various ), Folder 20-21)
  - Wiedergutmachung, Undated (Box 97 (19-Series 19 - Materials on various ), Folder 22)
  - Winnowing maching -- photos, Undated (Box 97 (19-Series 19 - Materials on various ), Folder 23)
  - Youth/Youth movement, Undated (Box 97 (19-Series 19 - Materials on various ), Folder 24)
  - Zagreb conference, Undated (Box 97 (19-Series 19 - Materials on various ), Folder 25)
  - Miscellaneous materials, Undated (Box 97 (19-Series 19 - Materials on various ), Folder 26)
  - Postwar U.S. and occupation newspapers, 19.171
    - Army talks, Undated (Box 97 (19-Series 19 - Materials on various ), Folder 27)
    - The Bavarian, Undated (Box 97 (19-Series 19 - Materials on various ), Folder 28)
    - The Dog Tag, Undated (Box 97 (19-Series 19 - Materials on various ), Folder 29)
    - E.T.I.S. News, Undated (Box 97 (19-Series 19 - Materials on various ), Folder 30)
    - New York Times Magazine, Undated (Box 97 (19-Series 19 - Materials on various ), Folder 31)
    - The New York Times Overseas Weekly, Undated (Box 97 (19-Series 19 - Materials on various ), Folder 32)
    - News of Germany, Undated (Box 97 (19-Series 19 - Materials on various ), Folder 33)
    - The Occupation Chronicle, Undated (Box 97 (19-Series 19 - Materials on various ), Folder 34)
    - The Stars and Stripes, Undated (Box 97 (19-Series 19 - Materials on various ), Folder 35)
    - Third U.S. Army Newsletter, Undated (Box 97 (19-Series 19 - Materials on various ), Folder 36)
    - Yank. The Army Weekly, Undated (Box 97 (19-Series 19 - Materials on various ), Folder 37)
- Series 20 - Miscellaneous memorabilia, 20; 188 file folders
  - Glass slides, Mount Everest, Undated (Box 98 (20-Series 20 - Miscellaneous memorabilia), Folder 1)
  - Keys, Undated (Box 98 (20-Series 20 - Miscellaneous memorabilia), Folder 2)
  - Audio tape, Undated (Box 98 (20-Series 20 - Miscellaneous memorabilia), Folder 3)
  - Theater programs, Undated (Box 98 (20-Series 20 - Miscellaneous memorabilia), Folder 4)
  - Retirement scrapbook, Undated (Box 98 (20-Series 20 - Miscellaneous memorabilia), Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous memorabilia, Undated (Box 98 (20-Series 20 - Miscellaneous memorabilia), Folder 6)
- Series 21 - Periodicals, 1911-1981; 21; 71 titles
  - Afrika und Übersee, (1975-1976) (Box 99 (21-Series 21 - Periodicals), Folder 1)
  - Allgemeine Zeitung, (1919) (Box 99 (21-Series 21 - Periodicals), Folder 2)
  - Anthropological Linguistics, (1976) (Box 99 (21-Series 21 - Periodicals), Folder 3)
  - Anthropologie / Anthropogenie, (1954) (Box 99 (21-Series 21 - Periodicals), Folder 4)
  - Archéocivilisation (Antiquités nationales et internationales), Undated (Box 99 (21-Series 21 - Periodicals), Folder 5)
  - Awake!, (1948) (Box 99 (21-Series 21 - Periodicals), Folder 6)
  - Bibliografiska meddelanden från Nordiska Museets Bibliotek, (1964-1965); (1969-1970); (1974-1975) (Box 99 (21-Series 21 - Periodicals), Folder 7)
  - Die Brücke. Übersetzungen aus der Weltpresse, (1948) (Box 99 (21-Series 21 - Periodicals), Folder 8)
  - Bulletin. American Anthropological Association, (1953-1959) (Box 99 (21-Series 21 - Periodicals), Folder 9)
  - Bulletin of the American Academy of Religion, (1969) (Box 99 (21-Series 21 - Periodicals), Folder 10)
  - Bulletin of the International Committee on Urgent Anthropological and Ethnological Research, (1979); (1981) (Box 99 (21-Series 21 - Periodicals), Folder 11)
  - The Christian Century, (1949) (Box 99 (21-Series 21 - Periodicals), Folder 12)
  - The Crisis, (1960) (Box 99 (21-Series 21 - Periodicals), Folder 13)
  - Deutsche Republik, (1930-1931) (Box 99 (21-Series 21 - Periodicals), Folder 14)
  - Deutsche Universitätszeitung, (1950) (Box 99 (21-Series 21 - Periodicals), Folder 15)
  - Deutscher Volksgeist, (1919) (Box 99 (21-Series 21 - Periodicals), Folder 16)
  - Discussions of Foreign Affairs, (1954) (Box 99 (21-Series 21 - Periodicals), Folder 17)
  - Folk-liv, (1940) (Box 99 (21-Series 21 - Periodicals), Folder 18)
  - Forschungen und Fortschritte, (1933) (Box 99 (21-Series 21 - Periodicals), Folder 19)
  - Fragen der Freiheit. Eine Schriftenreihe, (1961); (1969) (Box 99 (21-Series 21 - Periodicals), Folder 20)
  - Frankfurter Hefte, (1949) (Box 99 (21-Series 21 - Periodicals), Folder 21)
  - Future. A Journal of Modern World Issues by Students of Enfield High School, (1964); (1967) (Box 99 (21-Series 21 - Periodicals), Folder 22)
  - Die Godesberger Woche, (1934); (1936) (Box 99 (21-Series 21 - Periodicals), Folder 23)
  - Histoire Locale, (1953); (1960); (1962-1963) (Box 99 (21-Series 21 - Periodicals), Folder 24)
  - Idea and Experiment. A University at Work, (1952) (Box 99 (21-Series 21 - Periodicals), Folder 25)
  - Indian Voices, (1963-1966) (Box 99 (21-Series 21 - Periodicals), Folder 26)
  - Korrespondenzblatt der Deutschen Gesellschaft für Anthropologie / Ethnologie und Urgeschichte, (1911); (1923) (Box 99 (21-Series 21 - Periodicals), Folder 27)
  - Der Kreis / Le Cercle / The Circle, (1958) (Box 99 (21-Series 21 - Periodicals), Folder 28)
  - Das Landhaus, (1919) (Box 99 (21-Series 21 - Periodicals), Folder 29)
  - Das literarische Echo, (1919) (Box 99 (21-Series 21 - Periodicals), Folder 30)
  - Loma Matters, Undated (Box 100 (21-Series 21 - Periodicals), Folder 1)
  - Manas, (1951) (Box 100 (21-Series 21 - Periodicals), Folder 2)
  - Meddelanden. Institutionen för Folklivsforskning vid Lunds Universitet, (1970) (Box 100 (21-Series 21 - Periodicals), Folder 3)
  - Mitteilungen aus dem Museum für Völkerkunde, Leipzig, (1963); (1981-1983) (Box 100 (21-Series 21 - Periodicals), Folder 4)
  - Mitteilungen der Berliner Gesellschaft für Anthropologie, Ethnologie und Urgeschichte, (1968); (1971); (1973) (Box 100 (21-Series 21 - Periodicals), Folder 5)
  - Mitteilungsblatt der Gemeinschaft der rassisch und politisch verfolgten Christen e.V., (1947-1948) (Box 100 (21-Series 21 - Periodicals), Folder 6)
  - New South, (1949) (Box 100 (21-Series 21 - Periodicals), Folder 7)
  - Newsletter on Religious Inquiry, (1956) (Box 100 (21-Series 21 - Periodicals), Folder 8)
  - Notes Africaines. Bulletin d'information et de correspondence de l'Institut français d'Afrique noire, (1942-1943) (Box 100 (21-Series 21 - Periodicals), Folder 9)
  - Nyt fra Lejre, (1968) (Box 100 (21-Series 21 - Periodicals), Folder 10)
  - The Oral History Review 1979, Undated (Box 100 (21-Series 21 - Periodicals), Folder 11)
  - Phylon. The Atlanta University Review of Race & Culture, (1950) (Box 100 (21-Series 21 - Periodicals), Folder 12)
  - Plittersdorfer Heimatblätter, (1951) (Box 100 (21-Series 21 - Periodicals), Folder 13)
  - The Plough. The Quarterly of the Bruderhof Communities, (1954) (Box 100 (21-Series 21 - Periodicals), Folder 14)
  - Propaganda Dienst, (1944) (Box 100 (21-Series 21 - Periodicals), Folder 15)
  - Psychoanalytische Bewegung, (1931) (Box 100 (21-Series 21 - Periodicals), Folder 16)
  - RE. Review of Ethnology, (1974); (1976); (1982) (Box 100 (21-Series 21 - Periodicals), Folder 17)
  - Reformiertes Kirchenblatt -- isolated issues, (1928); (1932); (1934-1935); (1963-1964); (1969); (1971-1972); (1975) (Box 100 (21-Series 21 - Periodicals), Folder 18)
  - Reformiertes Kirchenblatt, (1976-1983) (Box 100 (21-Series 21 - Periodicals), Folder 19)
  - Religious Inquiry. Exploratory Studies on Empiric Approaches to Religion, (1960) (Box 100 (21-Series 21 - Periodicals), Folder 20)
  - Rundschreiben seiner Heiligkeit Pius' XI. Durch Gottes Vorsehung Papst, (1937) (Box 100 (21-Series 21 - Periodicals), Folder 21)
  - The Rural Visitor, (1961-1963) (Box 100 (21-Series 21 - Periodicals), Folder 22)
  - Schweizerland, (1915) (Box 100 (21-Series 21 - Periodicals), Folder 23)
  - Der Stern, (1929) (Box 100 (21-Series 21 - Periodicals), Folder 24)
  - Studium Generale, (1952) (Box 100 (21-Series 21 - Periodicals), Folder 25)
  - S.R.Z. Südwestdeutsche Rundfunk Zeitung, (1933) (Box 100 (21-Series 21 - Periodicals), Folder 26)
  - Die Tat, (1916/1917); (1919) (Box 100 (21-Series 21 - Periodicals), Folder 27)
  - Theologische Literaturzeitung, (1928) (Box 100 (21-Series 21 - Periodicals), Folder 28)
  - Le Trait d'Union de l'Eglise Méthodiste en Afrique du Nord, (1954); (1957-1959); (1962) (Box 100 (21-Series 21 - Periodicals), Folder 29)
  - Uranos. Blätter für ungeschmälertes Menschentum, (1922) (Box 100 (21-Series 21 - Periodicals), Folder 30)
  - Zeitschrift des Reichsbundes der höheren Beamten, (1928-1929) (Box 100 (21-Series 21 - Periodicals), Folder 31)
  - Zeitschrift des Vereines deutscher Ingenieure, (1894); (1902); (1915-1916) (Box 100 (21-Series 21 - Periodicals), Folder 32)
  - Zeitschrift für Ethnologie, (1982) (Box 100 (21-Series 21 - Periodicals), Folder 33)
  - Die Zukunft, (1900) (Box 100 (21-Series 21 - Periodicals), Folder 34)
  - Miscellaneous publications from the 1930s, Undated (Box 100 (21-Series 21 - Periodicals), Folder 35)
  - Union. Contemporary Cultural Review, XX, No.3 (March 1958) -- XXXVIII, No. 1 (April 1976), Undated (Box 101 (21-Series 21 - Periodicals), Folder 1)
    Missing: XX, No. 4-5, 7, 9, 11; XXII, No. 1; XXVI, No. 5; XXVII, No. 8; XXVIII, No. 3; XXX, No. 5; XXXII, No. 5, 7; XXXIII, No. 3; XXXIV, No. 2-4; XXXV, No. 1; XXXVII, No. 3-4.